Solon, Ohio. Solon Community Church records, 1897-2022.
Congregational Library & Archives
- "The Light" newsletter, 1953 2017; 1953-2017
  - "Light", 2017 (Box 7, File 40)
  - "Light", 1960 (Box 8, File 1)
  - "Light", 1961 (Box 8, File 2)
  - "Light", 1962 (Box 8, File 3)
  - "Light", 1963 1965; 1963-1965 (Box 8, File 4)
  - "Light", 1981 (Box 8, File 5)
  - "Light", 1982 (Box 8, File 6)
  - "Light", 1983 (Box 8, File 7)
  - "Light", 1984 (Box 8, File 8)
  - "Light", 1985 (Box 8, File 9)
  - "Light", 1986 (Box 8, File 10)
  - "Light", 1987 (Box 8, File 11)
  - "Light", 1988 (Box 8, File 12)
  - "Light", 1989 (Box 8, File 13)
  - "Light", 1990 (Box 8, File 14)
  - "Light", 1991 (Box 8, File 15)
  - "Light", 1992 (Box 8, File 16)
  - "Light", 1993 (Box 8, File 17)
  - "Light", 1994 (Box 8, File 18)